Guide to the William David Allred Papers 1969-002
University of Houston Libraries Special Collections
- Press File, 1972-1985
  - Press Clippings, September - October 1972 (Box 104)
  - Press Clippings, July - August 1972 (Box 104)
  - Press Clippings, June - December 1975 (Box 105)
  - Press Clippings (1-2), 1976 (Box 105)
  - Press Clippings (1-3), 1977 (Box 105)
  - Press Clippings, 1978 (Box 105)
  - Press Clippings, April 1979 (Box 105)
  - Press Clippings, August 1978 (Box 105)
  - Press Clippings, January 1979 (Box 105)
  - Press Clippings, January - July 1979 (Box 105)
  - Press Clippings (1-3), January 1980 (Box 105)
  - Press Clippings, 1983-1985 (Box 105)